These looks were easy to design
once I found my inspiration,
which is Central Park,
of course.
And it didn't need to be
complicated.
I said to the team,
"Let's make it chic,
"let's make it expensive,
and the clothes should feel like
a picnic in a Manet." You know?
And who is this
interesting fellow?
This is Mr. Spagooti.
He's a rock star.
The kids love him
like a sex god.
He's a traditional manga artist
from Tel Aviv
collaborating on
our athletic wear line.
We will incorporate his drawings
throughout the collection
like this.
With jacquard,
along with the number five
at the back
to commemorate our anniversary.
Get this girl a cigarette.
She's freezing. Come on.
Well, I've taken enough
of your time.
I'll leave you to your work.
It was great to see you again,
Chairman.
Oh, just before I forget,
just one more thing.
My grandson is a huge fan.
I-I heard. I will
send him a signed sample
as soon as they're in.
He would be most grateful.
They sell out too fast,
even for me.
Eniola will send a package over.
Okay. Fine.
- Whoa!
- Dope!
You remember that
Tommy Hilfiger thing?
Man, Tommy Hilfiger--
Is Tommy Gear owned
by a white person?
- It's got to be an Indian.
- He got to be Indian.
Hey, yo, dude coming down the
steps look like Drop Dead Fred.
- Good morning.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Hi. Good morning.
Oh.
Thank you so much
for meeting us
on such short notice.
We are so happy to meet you.
I am a little bit-- Look,
can we get some food first?
'Cause all I had was
that English breakfast,
and that did not hit,
so I need a real meal.
Yeah, anything you want.
Um, let's place a food order
right now. Yeah.
- All right, bet. You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
Can I get smoked ribs
with a dry rub?
And, um, let me get
a-a simple, God,
a simple-ass mac and cheese,
please. Thank you.
Certainly. And anything
for you, Earn?
Oh, I'm good.
Darius, you want anything?
Yeah. Jollof rice.
Jollof? I haven't heard of it.
It's as if your taste buds
are being scammed
by a Nigerian prince
at a Burna concert.
- Okay.
- One of those, please.
So, yes, uh, joll-of
for Darius.
And now that lunch is settled,
you've probably heard about
our little mix-up.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah...
Look, we want to apologize
to the community properly
with your help, you know.
All right, what I got to do?
So, nothing.
That's the beauty of it.
There's a press event later
where we'd introduce you
and the rest of our new
diversity advisory board
to our partnership.
And Eniola will be your liaison.
What's the financial aspect
to this?
We can't give you actual cash
'cause that would look
disingenuous.
But, well, we-we can donate
to any charity
or foundation of your choosing.
All right. Okay.
Uh, but I'm gonna need
a custom suit
for the press event.
A custom suit. Uh, yeah. Okay.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Okay.
Three.
Okay, yes. Three. Okay.
I need a bunch of clothes, too.
Free.
- Uh, yeah. Okay.
- Fine.
- Three years.
For three years.
- Whoa.
Three? In the studio
we'll try on a lot of clothes.
- A lot of clothes. Yeah. Mm-hmm.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Okay. Okay.
- Free tailoring, too.
Okay, easy.
Uh, I'll send the tailor up,
and you can then... Okay?
Gentlemen, it has been
such a pleasure.
Thank you so much.
Lovely to meet you.
And anything in the showroom
is yours, okay?
- Eh, even this?
- No, no. Except that.
- What you mean, man? Come on.
- Okay. Bye-bye, bye-bye.
It's, like, the most exclusive
thing you got.
What's up?
- We can talk later.
- No, nigga, say it now.
Man, he don't even
speak English anyway.
This feels like
an Uncle Tom photo op.
Why are we doing this?
Man, you know how hard it is
for me to get, like,
designer shit free
from my stylists, in Atlanta?
This way I'm plugged in.
Yeah, but you can
buy all that shit.
I shouldn't have to, man.
We work too damn hard.
This way we get free gifts,
runway seats,
free designer bags
for the thots, man.
Shit, my drip gonna
completely change.
You're not worried about,
you know,
what the streets think?
The streets?
Man, fuck the streets.
Man, I've shot niggas.
Finito. Should be two hours.
All right. Gracias.
Reputation.
You trying to tell me
that you, uh, you wouldn't take
any of these
free designer gifts?
Free shoes?
You wouldn't do that?
If it was me?
Yeah, I might still
do it, but...
I'd make sure they put me
on the board
for at least five years so I
could learn the infrastructure.
Then I'd start my own program.
Like teach Black people
how to reinvest
in their communities.
Like help out Black
entrepreneurs
and business owners.
Like a "reinvest in your hood"
campaign.
Something that might
actually help people.
Ooh, Lord, man, I don't know
why I asked,
'cause I knew you was
gonna be on that
"spook sitting by the door,"
Martin Luther King,
Ebeneezer Baptist Church shit.
- Goddamn, man. Like...
And you know what they do
to that dude every time.
- Yeah.
- Say it with me.
They kill him.
Thank you, man.
Try them shoes on.
Hi. I'm Sharon,
head of hospitality.
- Are you Darius?
- Yes.
Hi. Um, I got an email request
for jollof.
- Yeah.
- It's so weird.
My husband and I, we know every
Michelin place in town,
but I don't know that.
Is that--
It's Ghanaian, right?
No, no.
Who told you that?
Was it a Ghanaian?
No. No.
Um, it's just my mistake.
Is there a particular place
that you go to?
There is a place across town
that's supposed to be legendary.
It's just too out
of the way, but...
Oh, we can take you.
- Yeah? Are you sure?
- Yeah.
That's literally my job, babe.
We'll gather up
all the gift bags,
and I will call the car
around, yeah?
- Let's do it.
- Great.
- Hey, Sam.
- Hey, boo.
Mwah. Ooh, cute.
Thank you.
Uh, how are you not freezing?
Where are your pants?
Girl, I'm hot, if anything.
Khalil, you're a damn liar.
Beauty is pain.
Demarco.
That's Rose.
Voice of an angel.
Hi, I'm Khalil--
activist, writer, foodie.
I know who you are, man.
So, is this your first time
apologizing for white people?
- Apologizing?
- Yeah. It's the best.
The dinners are amazing.
I haven't paid for a meal
in 73 police shootings.
- Oh, I think we're on.
I forgive you.
This is probably some bullshit.
I am the least prejudiced
person in this room,
in the world, even.
So what do I do now,
just perform a couple of songs
or some shit?
After Bouchet is done
apologizing,
they'll open the floor
to questions.
Just say they didn't mean it,
smile and take these pictures.
We need to reflect,
- and we need to move on.
Hey. Relax, sweetie.
You got this.
And we are investigating
ourselves internally.
And now I proudly cede
to our panel of experts.
Clermont with Le Parisien.
Um, Paper Boi,
after this, is racism over?
Um...
- Fuck no. Obviously.
- Oh, my God.
I mean, look, la-- look
at the porn industry, right?
- They be having bitches...
- I think what he means
is that with our new initiative,
we believe racism
will be done by 2024.
Oh!
This movie is so crazy.
Yeah.
Is it Hamlet?
Not quite.
It's called Sharon Stone.
- It has a sequel.
- Ah.
The atmosphere in this place
is so cool.
- Oh?
- Yeah.
- Welcome to Eko Chops.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- I'm Mimi. Any drinks?
Uh, water's fine.
- Tap. Tap would be...
- Okay.
I'll be right back
to explain the menu.
- Okay.
- A-Actually, I know what I want.
I'm just gonna do Moin-Moin
with the egg or some liver.
Liver? Are you Naija?
- Yes, I'm Naija.
- Ooh.
Couldn't tell.
Your hair is so Igbo.
River State. Ijaw.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mm.
- Rivers boy?
- Yeah.
When was the last time you went?
- Uh, don't do this to me.
It's been too long.
The Moin-Moin is plain.
For next time, bring
your own meat or vegetable
you want them to put in.
The kitchen will cook
for you no problem.
Um, thank you, Auntie.
Oya, what you want to eat?
Uh...
Oh, I meant to ask you earlier,
what does "Naija" mean?
- Naija means Nigerian.
- Ah.
Yeah, this is
a Nigerian restaurant,
Nigerian food
and Nigerian music playing.
I see.
And apart from the goat,
this dish is exquisite.
Is it just rice?
- It's jollof. Naija jollof.
- Oh.
And what, what's she eating?
It's okra soup.
Ugh, I love her.
- Yeah, she's sweet.
- I need to get
her business card.
There is a lot
of growth potential.
Uh, my husband, he has
lots of commissary kitchens
all over the city.
It's all about good PR.
Cool.
Yes, mainly
fish and chip trucks,
but he's moving
into brick and mortar.
I'm actually joining him
full-time.
I feel like boneless fish
is an abomination.
Oh, God, I know. I hate fish.
I mean, I like fish,
but boneless fish is...
Is your Shazam working?
Mine's not working.
Homestretch.
Hope you're all rested.
Um, I'll be here to take notes
for the committee.
Alfred, why don't you go first?
What do you want
out of this meeting?
Shit, all right, okay. Uh...
You know, I'm--
This is something
I've been thinking about
for a long time, right?
So, you know,
obviously, everybody at this
table has the opportunity
- to help Black people.
- Right. Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Go on.
Yeah, so, um...
I was thinking
that we could do, like, a...
- like a capsule collection.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, a-and a campaign.
A campaign to, um,
teach Black people
how to reinvest
back into their communities.
- Hmm.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Demarco, what do you want?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I-I want the new
Off-White Nikes. Signed.
And a round trip to Mauritius,
business class.
- Mm-hmm.
- Business class, though.
- Sam?
I want 1,000 copies of my book
to be purchased
for sensitivity training.
She'll work on that.
I wish for ten tickets
to Raisin in the Sun,
for my charity,
and Julia Roberts
better be in it,
not an understudy
like last time.
- Mm-hmm.
- Ooh, and a hookup
to the new
Black Panther 2 premiere.
- Okay.
- Yeah, I could fuck
with some Black Panther tickets,
too, actually.
- Me, too.
- Black Panther tickets.
- Black Panther? The...?
- Yeah. The second film.
- Make sure it's
the second film, though.
- Right.
- Hey, hold-- hold up.
H-Hold the fuck...
How does any of that, man,
how does any of that
help Black people?
Shit, man, well, look, I'm Black
and it's helping me
a whole, a whole lot, so...
My nigga... are you Black?
Am I...
Am I, am I Black?
Khalil, man,
I don't, I don't even know
what your charity does, man.
It's in my book.
Buy a copy.
It's like Blue Man Group.
But activism.
It's quite genius.
- Al?
- Mm?
- No offense,
but we've been
in social justice awhile.
We know what we're doing.
That's fair. Yep.
I'm just saying
that Black people
don't really fuck with y'all
like that.
I mean, the streets
are saying that-that y'all
- full of shit, so...
- Uh, that's rude.
I mean, come on, man.
Like, we sitting here,
a bunch of Black people--
Black-adjacent influencers--
you know what I'm saying?
Like, I got a lot of ideas.
All right?
I can help you, you know?
If you listen to me, I mean,
you know, just hear me out.
...as soon as I get back,
all right?
It was good to see you.
Hey, um, is there
an Apple Store near here?
- I-I nicked my Watch.
- One moment, sir.
Hi.
Hey. How are you?
Fine.
Good.
What the hell's wrong with you?
What?
Where have you been?
I've been shopping.
I was thinking about
how Grace Jones
has all these, like, male suits,
and I kind of wanted one.
I also got this really cool,
like, '80s wig.
It's been weeks.
You give me a thumbs-up emoji?
Are you serious?
You guys are busy.
You're working.
I'm just kind of
doing my own thing.
It's not really
that big of a deal.
I mean, you guys didn't plan
for me to come here.
Yeah, you can't do that.
Okay? You can't just disappear.
Okay? We're parents.
I mean, what if something
had happened to you?
What if you were,
like, kidnapped?
I called your mom. She didn't
even know where you were.
Does your mom know
where you are right now?
I saw you. I saw what you did.
What?
You stole that from the shop.
This? I just bought this
at Christine's down the street.
You stole it and I am not going
to let you get away with it.
Because I'm Black and you think
I can't pay for it?
- Lady, I think
you've made a mistake.
Call the police. I am holding
you here till the police come.
- Hey. Let go of me.
What is wrong with you?
- Hey. Hey-- What...
- Let go of her.
You're just accusing people.
- Are you crazy?
No, it's all up to me.
You're going to jail.
What-- Get off!
- Is something wrong?
- Yes.
This woman came in
accusing my fiancée
of stealing a wig
that we just bought
- from Christine's.
- She stole it.
Ma'am, are you staying here?
- Uh, I am making
a citizen's arrest.
- Ma'am, leave this hotel
- or I will call the police.
I'm sorry for that, sir.
You know,
they can't find our bags,
they can't find our name
in the system,
they don't know
where our room is.
We're been sitting here
for hours.
She doesn't even like London.
I'm trying
to get her to move here,
and then this racist shit
happens.
- It's-it's unbelievable.
- Let me check on your room.
Regardless, we'll get you
a top room
free of charge for the night.
I can pay for the room.
I just want our bags.
The first night is on us.
Apologies, sir.
Are you staying here?
I am now.
All right, so
we open on a Black girl--
no, a Black woman--
and she is getting paid,
you heard,
'cause she's the boss, right?
So she's only going
to Black businesses
and she's giving her dollars
to the Black businesses,
you know, and one at a time,
just going,
"Hey, reinvest in your hood.
Reinvest in your hood."
And we should just
call that the, um...
Reinvest in Your Hood campaign.
Yeah, I wasn't
listening at first,
but that's actually
not a bad idea.
Yeah, we could do one
for Brixton, too.
- Mm.
- And we can, like,
include their social media
handles or something.
- Mm-hmm.
- Maybe you should think big,
- like scholarships.
- Hey.
- An apprenticeship program
with Black fashion students.
- Yes.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
If I had a sandwich
for every nigga
who thought he could
change something,
- I'd be Jimmy John.
- Yeah.
He's right, y'all. That shit
sounds expensive as hell.
I managed to squeeze out
a discretionary fund
of 60,000 euros.
Damn!
- - 60
- K? Girl, lead with that.
Well, that's a no-brainer.
Why don't we do it
through my organization
Open Arms?
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, hold up.
You got the
donation money last time, nigga.
- It's my turn.
- That little NAACP
endowment bullshit?
- That don't even count, man.
- Listen, that's not
how it works.
Hey, look, it's time
for Demarco
- to get his.
- Yeah, it don't sound right.
Over my handsome...
That don't sound right
when you say it.
Does he say "nigga" a lot?
- It just don't feel right.
- Decorum!
- Sit down, Dozle.
Why don't you sit down, Dozle?
- I wish you would, Khalil.
- Sit down, Dozle.
- Why don't you sit...
- Decorum! Decorum.
Sit your asses down.
Eniola, go ahead, baby.
It's Alfred's idea.
He decides.
Hey.
Do the right thing, brother.
Khalil.
I'll hammer out the details
with Marcello.
- Mm-hmm.
- Eniola, can you let Wendy
know I'd like
a five-minute meeting today
if possible?
- Mm-hmm.
- For real? So y'all...
Y'all really gonna do it?
- That's right.
- Ooh, we should get you
to film your own pitch
for Marcello.
Show him how passionate
you are about the campaign.
Yeah. All right.
Yeah, shit. Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Eniola, can you pack me
a to-go plate?
- I'm not your assistant.
- Meeting adjourned.
- Wow.
- Hey, what's up?
This is Paper Boi,
and I just want to throw
a pitch out there for you.
Uh, you know what I'm saying,
I just got this idea
about Black people making money,
you know what I'm saying,
and putting them Black dollars
in Black hands,
and then we just support
Black businesses, right?
'Cause if you take them dollars
and put them back
in your neighborhood,
your neighborhood will grow.
So I figure we just call it
the Reinvest in Your Hood
campaign, right?
You know what I mean, like,
just, like, think about it.
Reinvest in Your Hood.
Reinvest
in Your Hood.
Reinvest in Your Hood!
Yo! Darius.
Over here.
- How the hell are you?
- Sharon?
One s...
Uh, yeah, brown jollof,
- I'm lost.
- shredded carrots,
golden raisins,
- and kids jollof.
- Um, Eko Chops... What happened?
- Anything else?
- We were just there.
- Sharon. Sharon.
- Yeah, should be ready
in, like, ten minutes.
Yeah, see you then. Bye-bye.
Oh, my God,
I'm so glad to bump into you.
Surprise.
I quit my job
and we bought the place.
You bought the place?
Mm-hmm.
It's a-it's a Naija Bowl now.
Uh, grab a stool.
I'm coming out.
Oh, one Malibu
and one cheesy jollof.
Got it.
Yeah, so the landlord had been
trying to sell for months,
so we just, you know,
sweetened the pot.
So s-she relocated?
Where's Mimi?
I don't know. We actually...
We never exchanged info, so...
Dude, you've got to try this.
I want to get your thoughts.
What's in it?
It's a peach barbecue reduction
and chunks.
I call it The Darius,
'cause you're from Georgia.
Okay. Um...
Don't I gotta pay for this?
No. It's on me.
And your money
is literally no good here.
Card only.
Oh, a customer. BRB.
No. No.
Mm-mmm. Not doing that.
Uh, you should recycle that.
Thank you.
Hey, what's up? It's Paper Boi,
and I just want to throw a
pitch out there for you.
Reinvest in Your Hood.
Your Hood.
Think about it, 'cause if we
take them dollars and put them
back in your neighborhood,
your neighborhood will grow.
Reinvest in Your Hood.
Your Hood. Your Hood.
We're all from some hood, man.
Some hood.
We're all from some hood.
- We're all from some hood.
- Some hood.
We're all from some hood.
Reinvest in Your Hood.
- Reinvest in Your Hood.
- Your hood.
Reinvest in our hoods.
Yeah, see, y'all got
to invest shit.
Talking big money, nigga.
We're all from some hood.
Reinvest in Your Hood.
Reinvest in Your Hood!
Why the fuck can't I go in here?
That's some bullshit!
What the fuck y'all clapping
for, man? What's going on?
Monsieur Paper Boi,
your advertisement was super.
Oh, it's super...
I don't give a shit, nigga.
Y'all stole my shit.
What the fuck?
No, Al, we made the commercial.
You're not happy?
Nigga, you All Lives Matter-ed
my shit.
- Hell no I ain't happy.
- No, it's more inclusive,
uh, like this.
It's m-more attitude
of collaboration.
Hey, look, tell me this,
tell me this.
What y'all do about
the programs in Atlanta, huh?
We farmed it out
to the Red Cross, I believe.
- The Red Cross?!
- Yeah, you know,
like blood drives.
Nigga, I know what the fuck
the Red Cross is!
It's the worst one!
- Everybody needs blood.
- That ain't what
I asked for, man.
Them niggas ain't never gonna
see that fucking money now.
- Alfred, a word. Outside.
- What?! You tell me about
- the fucking Red Cross...
- Outside? Listen, listen.
What the fuck they gonna do
about that shit, man?
And they're supposed to call
it the... You supposed
- to reinvest...
- I need you to...
Get your hands off me!
- Listen, listen, relax.
- I'm talking to you...
Stop playing with me, man!
- Relax, relax.
- What I want to do
is go in there with a bat
- Oh, you want to go in there
and beat their asses...
- and knock they asses...
Yeah, I want to do that, man!
Why you ain't mad?
why?
Why would a company
make a project
that would teach Black people
to stop buying their products
and reinvest in their own?
- Man...
- W-Why would they fund
their own demise?
That's not a business.
That's a charity.
They were never gonna
make that commercial.
- That's why
you need your own nonprofit.
You control that money.
That's how I managed
- to squeeze 100
- K out of them
for my own charity.
Look, I told you,
I've been doing
this social justice thing
a long time.
Hey. Look, Black Panther
premiere is coming up.
Do you want to go?
Got an extra ticket.
No, man.
Whoopi Goldberg and Larenz Tate
are in this one.
Larenz Tate.
- Larenz Tate, hmm?
- Mm-hmm.
No. No, I'm-I'm good. I'm good.
I'm good.
All right, suit yourself.
Think about what I said.
What's up?!
Do you remember on Nickelodeon
around Halloween
they'd have Nick or Treat?
Like "trick or treat"
on-on Nickelodeon?
Oh, yeah, I think I do, yeah.
Think about that.
- Nigga Treat.
- I never heard "Nick or Treat."
I've been playing this song
all over Europe.
You know it?
Yeah, I know this song.
It's pretty.
This surround sound is so good.
Mmm.
I'm sorry about, um...
earlier.
What do you mean?
Before the lady, I...
kind of felt
like I was attacking you.
I was just worried.
Oh, Earn.
You worry about everything.
That's not true.
Yeah, it is.
But you shouldn't be.
You know,
Darius says that...
this is all a simulation.
Yeah, that sounds like him.
Did you, um...
did you steal that wig?